yo yo look if I actually want to like
make it as a rapper I gotta write songs
I was a child in the 90s tikka ride with
me
while we all recall wall ball and prank
phone calls bumpers for you bowling ball
I may be hitting them all because it's
his New Jersey and stay up late but
still wake up early to get to school
your seat belt buckles were pokemons
cars taught me how to hustle and kids
rode orgy on their backpacks what does
that mean my parents left home to be
even named googling I thought a splash
screen that asked me if I was a teen
well basically of course I'm sure how
does the computer know when it was born
a generation for later net porn
flip looking back to high school romance
is all the way back to the little school
dances prancing around like has nothing
to prove because I was just a little kid
with nothing to lose and I was not cool
but not self-conscious telling the
school they were teaching a monster
total bullshit that was totally bonkers
and only grow when I was acting
obnoxious I was brought about in my
class an asshole who barely passed whole
town's template super smash the senior
level up your ass and you
it's all happened a while ago but let's
go back
let's start the show
[Music]